Stafford, Ronald B.; Papers apap217
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Legislation, 1974-2002; 9; 32.51 cubic ft.
  - An Act to Authorizing Each of the Town Boards of the Towns of Crown Point, Essex, Jay, Keene, Lewis, Moriah, North Hudson, Schroon, Westport and Willsboro, All Located in Essex County, Upon the Adoption of a Proposition Duly Submitted to Appropriate and P, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 110)
  - An Act to Amend the Real Property Tax Law, in Relation to the Partial Tax Exemption for Real Property Owned by Persons 65 Years of Age or Over, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 111)
  - An Act to Amend the Agriculture and Markets Law, in Relation to Making Prepackaged Fruits and Vegetables Sold at Retail Available in Smaller Quantities, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 112)
  - An Act to Amend the Private Housing Finance Law and the Real Property Tax Law, in Relation to Changing the Purpose of Mortgage Loan Authorization from the Construction of Community Senior Citizen Centers to the Construction of Senior Citizen Housing, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 113)
  - An Act to Amend the Environmental Conservation Law, in Relation to Granting Free Fishing and Hunting Licenses to Persons 65 Years of Age or Older, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 114)
  - An Act to Amend the Penal Law, in Relation to Terms of Imprisonment Concurrent or Consecutive with Terms of Other Jurisdictions, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 115)
  - Abolishment of the Office of Parks and Recreation and Transferring the Functions, Powers, and Duties to the Department of Environmental Conservation, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 116)
  - An Act to Amend the Public Service Law, in Relation to Increasing the Membership of the Public Service Commission, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 117)
  - An Act to Amend the Executive Law, in Relation to Adirondack Park Agency Powers as to Reservoirs, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 118)
  - Tax Interest Exemption, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 119)
  - An Act to Amend the Labor Law, in Relation to Unemployment Insurance for Public School Employees, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 120)
  - Establish a Waste Oil Collection System Designed to Recapture, Rerefine and Reuse Waste Oil in New York State, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 121)
  - Concurrent Resolution of the Senate and Assembly Proposing an Amendment to Article 7 of the Constitution, in Relation to Standing for Citizens to Sue to Challenge the Constitutionality of a State Law, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 122)
  - An Act to Amend the Vehicle and Traffic Law, in Relation to Equipment Violations in Certain Cases, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 123)
  - An Act to Authorize the State Comptroller to Pay to School District No. 1 of the Town of Bellmont a Sum of Money for Taxes on State-Owned Lands, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 124)
  - An Act to Amend the Environmental Conservation Law, in Relation to Free Licenses for Persons 62 Years of Age or Older and Repealing Paragraph D of Subdivision 4 of Section 11-0713 Thereof, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 125)
  - Joint Resolution of the Senate and Assembly Expressing Gratitude to the Director of Camp Dudley, the Oldest Boy Camp in the United States, for the Role Camp Dudley has Played in the Development of Young Men Attending Such Camp, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 126)
  - An Act to Amend the Criminal Procedure Law, in Relation to Youthful Offender Procedures, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 127)
  - An Act to Amend the Executive Law, in Relation to Requiring Permits for the Conveyance of an Interest in Real Property, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 128)
  - An Act to Amend the Criminal Procedure Law, in Relation to Peremptory Challenges of Jurors, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 129)
  - An Act to Amend the Penal Law, in Relation to the Definition of Convicted for Purposes of the Firearms Statute, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 130)
  - An Act to Amend the Criminal Procedure Law, in Relation to Securing a Defendant's Appearance for Arraignment, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 131)
  - An Act to Amend the Criminal Procedure Law, in Relation to Examination of Defendants who Interpose a Defense of Not Guilty by Reason of Mental Disease or Defect, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 132)
  - An Act to Amend the Administrative Code of the City of New York and the County Law, in Relation to the Removal of Organs from Bodies Under the Jurisdiction of a Coroner or Medical Examiner, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 133)
  - Concurrent Resolution of the Senate and Assembly Proposing an Amendment to Article 7 of the Constitution, in Relation to Standing for Citizens to Sue to Bar Unconstitutional Expenditures of State Funds or to Challenge Unconstitutional Actions by State Off, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 134)
  - An Act to Amend the Environmental Conservation Law, in Relation to Off-Road Recreational Vehicles, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 135)
  - Air Pollution Control Violations, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 136)
  - Penalties for Violating Laws Protecting Tidal Wetlands, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 137)
  - Making Prepackaged Fruits and Vegetables Sold at Retail Available in Smaller Quantities, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 138)
  - Allow Any Local Government Agency to Lease Dwelling Units from Public Housing Authorities, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 139)
  - Real Property Tax Exemptions for Senior Citizens, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 140)
  - Senior Citizen Eligibility for Partial Real Property Tax Exemptions, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 141)
  - Creation of a Junior Big Game Archery License, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 142)
  - Authorize Free or Reduced Admission Rates to State Parks for Senior Citizens, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 143)
  - Increase the State Reimbursement Rate for School Lunches, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 144)
  - Eliminate Social Security from Income for Real Property Tax Exemption for Senior Citizens, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 145)
  - Require the Use of all Highway Tolls and Taxes to be Used Solely on the State Highways, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 146)
  - Construction of Public Housing for Elderly Persons, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 147)
  - Filing Zoning Regulations and Amendments in the County Clerk's Office, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 148)
  - Authorize Promotion and Development of Winter and Summer Recreational Facilities by the Essex Industrial Development Agency, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 149)
  - Granting Retirement Credit for Military Service, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 150)
  - Four Years of Tuition-Free Higher Education to Former Vietnam Prisoners, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 151)
  - Establish a Revolving Fund for Operation of the Parks and Playgrounds District, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 152)
  - Mandate Membership on the Municipal Police Training Council to be Partially Selected from Police Conference of New York, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 153)
  - Establishing an Arts and Handcrafts Committee in the Department of Commerce, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 154)
  - Preventing Pollution of Classified Surface Waters, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 155)
  - Removal of Inequity for Reappraisal of All Property in a Taxing Jurisdiction, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 156)
  - Use of Authorized Ambulance and Police Snowmobiles, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 157)
  - Providing State Funding of Certain County Transportation Services to Senior Citizens, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 158)
  - Increasing the Membership of the Public Service Commission, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 159)
  - Provide Regents Scholarships for Children of Deceased Vietnam Veterans, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 160)
  - Prohibit Abandonment of Public Roads that Afford Direct Access to Forest Preserve Lands, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 161)
  - Providing a State Plan for the Coordination of County Programs Protecting Vulnerable Older Persons, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 162)
  - Give Local Governments in the Adirondacks the Right to Zone their Own Communities, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 163)
  - Expungment of Certain Criminal Records, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 164)
  - Incorporate the Adirondack Park Agency into the DEC, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 165)
  - Merge the Special Improvement Districts of Queensbury into One Single Water District, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 166)
  - Mandatory Coverage of Insurance for Plate Glass Coverage, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 167)
  - Make State Responsible for All Forest Fire Fighting Charges, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 168)
  - Permit the Unsworn Testimony of a Child Over 12 to be Used in Certain Trials, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 169)
  - Maintain the Port of Albany in a State of Operational Repair, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 170)
  - Construction of Low Cost Senior Citizen Housing, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 171)
  - Lower the Age Required to Receive a Free Fishing and Hunting License, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 172)
  - Establish a New York State Heart and Hypertension Center within the Department of Health, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 173)
  - Requires State to First Offer Used Highway Equipment to Local Governments at Reduced Costs, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 174)
  - Insure Proper Protection and Representation of the Consumer by the Consumer Protection Board, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 175)
  - Rights of Lottery Sales Agents, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 176)
  - Provide Representation for Retired Teachers through Membership on the Teachers' Retirement Board, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 177)
  - Dissolve the Public Hospital District Established in Elba in 1927, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 178)
  - Prohibits Campaign Literature or Posters on Highways or within the Limits or Right of Way on any Public Road, 1975 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 179)
  - Co-Legislation, 1975-1977 (Box 2 (9-Legislation), Folder 180)
  - Co-Legislation, 1975-1977 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 1-2)
  - Authorizing the Trustees of the State University of New York to Lease Unused Real Property to Non-Profit Organizations for the Purpose of Constructing Dormitories and Student Housing Facilities, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - An Act to Amend the Environmental Conservation Law, in Relation to Minimum Size Limits for Muskellunge Taken from the St. Lawrence River, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 4)
  - An Act to Amend the Environmental Conservation Law, in Relation to the Taking of Wild Hen Pheasants in St. Lawrence County, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - Joint Resolution of the Senate and Assembly of the State of New York Memorializing to Repeal Title XX of the Social Security Act, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 6)
  - Joint Resolution of the Senate and Assembly of the State of New York Memorializing Congress to Enact Welfare Reform, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - An Act to Amend the Education Law, in Relation to the Designation of a Bank by the Bolton Central School District, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 8)
  - Allow Graduate Students to Exclude Parental Income for Financial Reasons, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 9)
  - Authorize the Establishment of a Public Parks and Play Grounds District in the Town of North Elba, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - Relief to an Appellant who has Failed at Taking Prescribed Appeal Steps, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 11)
  - Require State Ski Facilities to Allow School Districts to Utilize their Facilities for Free, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - Creating Technical Assistance Centers at Plattsburgh and Binghamton, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 13)
  - Allow BOCES to Continue Contractual Transportation Arrangements, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - Reduce Probationary Period for Tenure at CUNY Schools, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 15)
  - Twenty Year Half Pay Pension for Correction Officers, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 16)
  - Legislative Approval of New Full-Time Resident Members of the APA, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - Allow Visiting Fishermen to Use a Three Day Fishing License, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 18)
  - Review of Regional Projects by the Adirondack Park Agency, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - Major Reforms to the Hearing Aid Industry, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - Designate Special Deer Management Areas in the Northern Zone, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - Inclusion of Students on the Board of Trustees and Advisory Council of HESC, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 22)
  - Provide Departmental Exemptions for Certain School Bus Equipmental Requirements, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 23)
  - Requires Public Interest Groups to File Application with Secretary of State, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 24)
  - Permit Conveyance of Adirondack Forest Preserve Land to the Siberian Rod and Gun Club, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 25)
  - Provides for Public Enactment and Approval of Laws (Initiative and Referendum), 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 26)
  - Authorize the Board of Education to Contract a Commercial Bank to Collect Taxes, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 27)
  - Allowing County Legislatures to Contract with Non-Public Two-Year Colleges, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 28)
  - Creates and Continues 600 Scholarships for 1976-1977 War Service (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 29)
  - Provide Additional Regulation of Hearing Aid Dealers, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 30)
  - Grant Statutory Authorization to Municipalities to Lease Purchased Items of Personal Property, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 31)
  - Offer Public Access to Additional Lobbyist Registration Information Filed with the Secretary of State, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 32)
  - Prohibits an Individual from Receiving Public Assistance and Workers' Compensation at the Same Time, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 33)
  - Allows HESC to Exchange Data with the New York State Tax Division to Verify Financial Needs Data, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 34)
  - Strengthen Statutes Detailing Fire Inspection Requirements for College Campuses, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 35)
  - Legalizes and Confirms Actions Taken Involving the Queensbury Water District, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 36)
  - Continuing High School Education, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 37)
  - Establish County Water and Sewer Districts in Warren and Washington Counties, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 38)
  - Creation of the Glens Falls Industrial Development Agency, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 39)
  - Increase Amount of Money Given to a Released Inmate, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 40)
  - Requires Individuals and Corporations to Include Their Residence when Filing Real Property Conveyances, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 41)
  - Partial Funding of the Master Planning Expense of the Commission on Independent Colleges and Universities, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 42)
  - Exclude Notice of Tax Sale when Sold without Competitive Bidding, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 43)
  - Allow the DEC to Extend Fishing Seasons in Lake Champlain's Tributaries, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 44)
  - Appropriates Funding of an Admissions Referral and Information Center, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 45)
  - Legislative Approval of Adirondack Park Local Land Use Programs, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 46)
  - Require Publishment Detailing State Assistance Programs to Local Governments, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 47)
  - Allowing Only One Application for a Certificate Granting Leave to Appeal, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 48)
  - Eliminates Proof of Mailing a Tax Notice to be Filed with County Treasurer's Office, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 49)
  - Minimum Wage and Payment for Prison Labor, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 50)
  - Provide Civil Proceeding and Penalties for the Adirondack Private Land Use Law, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 51)
  - Increase State Aid Awarded to CUNY Schools, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 52)
  - Authorize State University Construction Fund to Award Turnkey Contracts based on Performance Specifications, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 53)
  - CUNY Construction Fund, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 54)
  - Give the DEC the Authority to Regulate Black Bear Season, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 55)
  - Require the Formulation of an Immediate Disaster Plan, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 56)
  - An Act to Amend the Education Law, in Relation to Resubmission of Budget in Certain Cases, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 57)
  - An Act to Amend the Parks and Recreation Law, in Relation to the State-Wide Trails System and Making Appropriations, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 58)
  - Authorizing the Village of Keeseville to Fund Certain Outstanding Revenue Anticipation Renewal Notes by the Issuance of Bonds or Bond Anticipation Notes, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 59)
  - An Act to Amend the Education Law, in Relation to Additional Student Loans for Medical or Dental Students, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 60)
  - An Act to Amend the Education Law, in Relation to Providing Sponsor Indemnity for Officers and Employees of Community Colleges, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 61)
  - Creation of the Glens Falls Industrial Development Agency, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 62)
  - An Act to Amend the Education Law, in Relation to Additional Student Loans for Medical or Dental Students, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 63)
  - Legalizes and Confirms Actions Taken Involving the Former Queensbury Water District, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 64)
  - An Act to Amend the Education Law, in Relation to the Exclusion of Parental Income in the Determination of the Amount of an Award, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 65)
  - An Act to Amend the Education Law, in Relation to the Expenditure of Excess Student Revenues for Community Colleges, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 66)
  - An Act to Amend the Environmental Conservation Law, in Relation to Streams Classified N and Waters Suitable for Trout Spawning, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 67)
  - An Act to Amend the Environmental Conservation Law, in Relation to Eliminating Errors, Inconsistencies, and Nonconformities, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 68)
  - An Act to Amend the Tax Law, in Relation to Certain Prohibited Employment Practices Related to Lottery Sales Agents, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 69)
  - Permit BOCES District #7 to enter Transportation Contracts with the Counties of Clinton, Essex, Warren, Washington, and Hamilton Counties, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 70)
  - An Act to Amend the Education Law, in Relation to Extending Full Speaking Privileges to Non-Voting Student Members at Various Higher Educational Institutions, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 71)
  - Authorize the Establishment of Certain County Water and Sewer Districts in Washington and Warren Counties, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 72)
  - An Act to Amend the Education Law, in Relation to the Expenditure of Excess Student Revenues for Community Colleges, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 73)
  - An Act to Amend the Criminal Procedure Law, in Relation to Appeals to Intermediate Appellate Courts, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 74)
  - Concurrent Resolution of the Senate and Assembly Proposing the Addition of a New Article to the Constitution Relating to Initiative and Referendum and Recall, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 75)
  - An Act to Amend the Tax Law, in Relation to Certain Prohibited Employment Practices Related to Lottery Sales Agents, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 76)
  - Appropriation for a Special One Year Program of Grants to 1976-77 SUNY Seniors (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 77)
  - An Act to Amend the Education Law, in Relation to Providing Sponsor Indemnity for Officers and Employees of Community Colleges, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 78)
  - An Act to Amend the Education Law, in Relation to the Designation of a Bank by the Bolton Central School District, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 79)
  - An Act to Amend the Environmental Conservation Law, in Relation to Streams Classified N and Waters Suitable for Trout Spawning, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 80)
  - An Act to Amend the Tax Law, in Relation to Certain Refunds on the Tax Imposed Motor Fuel, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 81)
  - An Act to Amend the Environmental Conservation Law, in Relation to Eliminating Errors, Inconsistencies, and Nonconformities, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 82)
  - An Act to Amend the Tax Law, in Relation to Certain Refunds on the Tax Imposed Motor Fuel, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 83)
  - Authorizing the Trustees of the State University of New York to Lease Unused Real Property to Non-Profit Organizations for the Purpose of Constructing Dormitories and Student Housing Facilities, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 84)
  - An Act to Amend the Education Law, in Relation to Additional Student Loans for Medical or Dental Students, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 85)
  - Appropriation to Restore State University Scholarships for Graduate and Professional Students, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 86)
  - Establishment of Technical Assistance Centers in Plattsburgh and Binghamton, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 87)
  - Exceptions to from the Forever Wild Provisions with Respect to Lands Located within the Forest Preserve, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 88)
  - Require Publishment Detailing State Assistance Programs to Local Governments, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 89)
  - An Act to Amend the Education Law, in Relation to College Fire Inspections and Repealing Various Subdivision 12 of Section Eight Hundred Seven-b of Such Law Relating to the Limitation of Applicability of Such Section, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 90)
  - An Act to Amend the Education Law, in Relation to Providing Free Public Schools to Resident Pupils, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 91)
  - An Act to Amend the Vehicle and Traffic Law, in Relation to Providing for Departmental Exemptions for Certain Equipment Requirements for School Buses, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 92)
  - An Act to Amend the Environmental Conservation Law, in Relation to Taking of Wild Hen Pheasants in St. Lawrence County, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 93)
  - An Act to Amend the Public Office Law, in Relation to Open Meetings by an Agency or Office Thereof, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 94)
  - Abolishment of the Office of Parks and Recreation and Transferring the Functions, Powers, and Duties to the Department of Environmental Conservation, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 95)
  - An Act to Amend the Education Law, in Relation to Assisting the New York State Higher Education Services Corporation in Carrying out its Present Powers to Verify the Income Statements of Applicants for Financial Aid, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 96)
  - An Act to Amend the Navigation Law, in Relation to Ice Fishing Shanties on Lake George, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 97)
  - An Act to Amend the Education Law, in Relation to Contracts with Non-Public Two-Year Colleges in Counties not Having Community Colleges, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Legislation), Folder 98)